(Sheldon:)There's no excuse for that.
(Sheldon:)And I'm truly sorry.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)I appreciate that.
(Sheldon:)I want you to know
that that is sincere.
I-I do feel bad.
(Sheldon:)I'm not just saying it
to be included on your trip.
(Leonard:)Appreciate that, too.
(Sheldon:)Terrific.
(Sheldon:)Now all that's left
is for you to invite me to come.
Me to ask, “Are you sure?”
You to say, “Absolutely.”
(Sheldon:)And then me
to bring it home with,
“How could I say no
to that face?”
(Leonard:)You're still not coming.
What? But I apologized
and I meant it.
(Sheldon:)I know that we don't play
this game very often,
(Sheldon:)but you're doing it wrong.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I accept
your apology, but you upset
(Leonard:)a lot of people
while you were sick.
(Leonard:)I'm not in a position
to just say you can come.
(Sheldon:)Well, all right.
(Sheldon:)What if I apologize
to all of them?
(Leonard:)Fine, if you
apologize to everyone,
(Leonard:)they all say it's okay,
then yes, you can come.
Challenge accepted!
(Sheldon:)Sounds like it's time for
the Sheldon Cooper Apology Tour.
(Leonard:)Well, I hope
it's as much fun
(Leonard:)as the Sheldon Cooper
Spell-Checks Local Menus Tour.